[
  {
    "id": "197c1fceb9d6",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which hobby should I fake for clout?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which hobby should i fake for clout?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Roller skating",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ceramics",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "BookTok influencer",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "44",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.673320",
    "timer": 21379,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 14,
    "likes": 8,
    "comments": 4,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "fe5bb05dbb6e",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "How do you survive family dinners?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: how do you survive family dinners?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "One-word replies",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Bathroom breaks every 10 min",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Pretending to take calls",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "60",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.673657",
    "timer": 33393,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 3,
    "likes": 128,
    "comments": 6,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "5d1614e020ce",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "What\u2019s your love language today?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: what\u2019s your love language today?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Cash App emojis",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Spotify playlist titles",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Overexplaining in texts",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "7",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.673819",
    "timer": 12021,
    "pledge": 1.69,
    "tipCount": 2,
    "likes": 256,
    "comments": 8,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "53dd7d73f916",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which weekend vibe are you craving?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which weekend vibe are you craving?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Netflix & ignore responsibilities",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Bubble bath + overthinking",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Solo karaoke meltdown",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "62",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.674372",
    "timer": 31265,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 11,
    "likes": 173,
    "comments": 1,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "b5d82fbfd6ab",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "What\u2019s your love language today?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: what\u2019s your love language today?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Cash App emojis",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Spotify playlist titles",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Overexplaining in texts",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "37",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.674694",
    "timer": 42988,
    "pledge": 9.69,
    "tipCount": 10,
    "likes": 29,
    "comments": 6,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "508a7b6648db",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which music genre heals heartbreak best?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which music genre heals heartbreak best?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "90s R&B",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Trap soul",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Acoustic sad-girl covers",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "7",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.674806",
    "timer": 39813,
    "pledge": 1.0,
    "tipCount": 5,
    "likes": 124,
    "comments": 7,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "b604b80b9afb",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "How do you survive family dinners?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: how do you survive family dinners?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "One-word replies",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Bathroom breaks every 10 min",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Pretending to take calls",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "15",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.674918",
    "timer": 43550,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 9,
    "likes": 122,
    "comments": 4,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "5ec1de69d140",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which passive-aggressive move is elite?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which passive-aggressive move is elite?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Leaving the chat",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Loudly sipping drink",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Smiling with no eye contact",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "69",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675024",
    "timer": 10354,
    "pledge": 6.48,
    "tipCount": 8,
    "likes": 231,
    "comments": 5,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "9f1efdab0543",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which hobby should I fake for clout?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which hobby should i fake for clout?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Roller skating",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ceramics",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "BookTok influencer",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "68",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675094",
    "timer": 29577,
    "pledge": 2.43,
    "tipCount": 15,
    "likes": 43,
    "comments": 1,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "bd89b5721d34",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which emoji says 'I\u2019m unwell' the loudest?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which emoji says 'i\u2019m unwell' the loudest?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "\ud83d\ude35\u200d\ud83d\udcab",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "\ud83e\udee0",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "\ud83d\ude2c",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "4",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675459",
    "timer": 357,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 4,
    "likes": 32,
    "comments": 0,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "1e73d62518e1",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which type of friend are you in the group chat?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which type of friend are you in the group chat?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "The memer",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "The responder two hours late",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "The one typing and deleting",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "49",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675788",
    "timer": 30511,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 12,
    "likes": 36,
    "comments": 7,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "a7eb6bdc32a1",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "How should I handle being left on read?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: how should i handle being left on read?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Send a meme",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Unsend the last message",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Text their best friend",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "34",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675918",
    "timer": 33914,
    "pledge": 2.53,
    "tipCount": 15,
    "likes": 228,
    "comments": 7,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "a060d5229e09",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "How do you flex your soft life?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: how do you flex your soft life?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Post your smoothie",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Skip meetings",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Order delivery twice",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "42",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675964",
    "timer": 12045,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 14,
    "likes": 249,
    "comments": 5,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "abfe48b91877",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "How do you flex your soft life?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: how do you flex your soft life?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Post your smoothie",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Skip meetings",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Order delivery twice",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "32",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.675983",
    "timer": 32012,
    "pledge": 1.44,
    "tipCount": 7,
    "likes": 42,
    "comments": 7,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "b2c638a45449",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which weekend vibe are you craving?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which weekend vibe are you craving?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Netflix & ignore responsibilities",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Bubble bath + overthinking",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Solo karaoke meltdown",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "42",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676012",
    "timer": 16845,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 14,
    "likes": 161,
    "comments": 3,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "c1824720f03a",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which hobby should I fake for clout?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which hobby should i fake for clout?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Roller skating",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ceramics",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "BookTok influencer",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "57",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676034",
    "timer": 29637,
    "pledge": 1.97,
    "tipCount": 6,
    "likes": 293,
    "comments": 4,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "53769cc87855",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Best way to humble a hater?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: best way to humble a hater?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Glow-up montage",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Silent success",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Clapback via meme",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "34",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676049",
    "timer": 5497,
    "pledge": 2.2,
    "tipCount": 8,
    "likes": 238,
    "comments": 5,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "b25817463dbb",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Best way to humble a hater?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: best way to humble a hater?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Glow-up montage",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Silent success",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Clapback via meme",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "24",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676071",
    "timer": 10020,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 15,
    "likes": 91,
    "comments": 1,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "9d86f4afe454",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "What's your toxic work habit?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: what's your toxic work habit?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Working through lunch",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "Pretending to be busy",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "Replying \u2018on it\u2019 to everything",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "51",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676087",
    "timer": 34795,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 13,
    "likes": 106,
    "comments": 7,
    "nsfw": false
  },
  {
    "id": "30c9868f2172",
    "type": "three-option",
    "question": "Which type of friend are you in the group chat?",
    "description": "Community-driven feedback: which type of friend are you in the group chat?",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "The memer",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3Ilaqcg"
      },
      {
        "text": "The responder two hours late",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/447OtGd"
      },
      {
        "text": "The one typing and deleting",
        "votes": 0,
        "affiliateLink": "https://amzn.to/3TUNcw5"
      }
    ],
    "creatorId": "67",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-30T09:32:38.676103",
    "timer": 33959,
    "pledge": 0,
    "tipCount": 5,
    "likes": 137,
    "comments": 8,
    "nsfw": false
  }
]